Excuse me.
So lively!
Why are they all wearing masks?
I forgot.
Tonight is the Qiqiao Festival.
It's an old tradition.
Wearing a mask to hide your identity
allows you to boldly seek out a connection
amidst the vast crowd.
I see.
Let's go.
Let's pick one.
Young master, young lady,
do you want a mask?
Pick whatever you like.
Does it look good?
Yes.
It suits you.
Boss,
sugar-coated haws.
Sugar-coated haws!
Sugar-coated haws, fragrant and crispy!
Do you want to eat?
I'll buy for you.
Sugar-coated haws!
Miss,
draw a fortune,
it's very efficacious.
How much is it?
Ah,
today is the Qiqiao Festival,
It's free.
My name is Xiaoguo.
I want to pray for my parents, brother,
Hua and Huang.
I just lost it.
Can I have another one?
Well,
you can only
draw one a year.
Or it won't
come true.
Little boy,
this one is for you.
Sister, you gave it to me?
How will you
pray for your parents?
My parents
are no longer with me.
It's for you.
Thank you, sister.
This one is for you.
I hope you like it.
Thank you,
generous stranger.
Xiao Wan.
Generous stranger,
could you do me another favor?
Write my name,
Ling Shenxing, on it,
and hang it on the highest spot.
Thank you.
Is it delicious?
Yes.
By the way,
you are always around girls.
Can you help me see
which brand of handkerchief
is in my bag?
It's a popular brand a few years ago.
Now,
it's not popular anymore.
I've been following Chu Nanfeng's carriage.
and sent you back home.
He didn't go anywhere else.
[You left me]
[a life-saving pill,]
[but you chose to]
[follow him.]
[Su Muwan,]
[who do you like?]
[I'm sure]
[it's Ling Shenxing.]
Everyone's here.
I have something to announce today.
When Second Concubine gave birth,
I promised Jinrou
that if the child was born safely,
she would be made a wife.
So,
now,
it's time to fulfill the promise.
[Will Ling Shenxing agree?]
Be happy.
After all, it's a happy event.
Mu Wan,
as a wife,
we shouldn't be
too stingy.
Let's take some time
these days
to take Jinrou out
to socialize.
Okay.
There are several good days this month.
You can choose one.
The situation in the northwest is tense.
I have no interest in this.
Xing.
It's okay, Madam.
Jinrou, it's okay.
I've recently
learned several more pleasant tunes.
I'll sing for you, shall I?
[This dead green tea is performing again.]
She sings better than she talks.
So disgusting.
It's good.
If you like it,
I'll sing for you every day.
Okay?
Okay.
Go back and sit down.
Su Muwan,
I don't believe you can outdo me in everything.
Miss Ye is already so excellent.
I wonder how well
the Young Madam, known as
the most beautiful woman in Yang City, can sing.
It's not that easy to embarrass me.
Let's eat.
The dishes will get cold.
Singing Kunqu Opera
is so boring.
How about
I sing a new song for you?
A new song?
Fine.
Sing one.
Let's see.
What?
Show off again.
It's really new.
Sounds good.
Your poison hasn't been cured.
You should be careful of everyone around you.
Even if it's a maid brought by the Su Family,
you should also be careful.
Instead of being on guard,
why not kill the root?